[
  {
    "question": "An IT Engineer needs to create a Virtual Machine in Azure.\nCurrently, the IT Engineer has an Android OS based workstation.\nWhich of the following can the IT Engineer use to create the desired Virtual Machine in Azure.\n[select 3]",
    "options": {
      "A": "Microsoft PowerApps",
      "B": "Azure Cloud Shell",
      "C": "Azure Powershell",
      "D": "Azure CLI"
    },
    "answer": "BCD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following customers are eligible to use\nAzure Government to develop a cloud solution.\n(Select TWO)",
    "options": {
      "A": "Canadian government contractors.",
      "B": "European government contractors",
      "C": "United States government entities",
      "D": "United States government contractors"
    },
    "answer": "CD"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to set up an Azure Free Account.\nDoes the Standard Support plan come along with the Azure Free Account?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to use its Azure Free Account for hosting production-based resources.\nDoes the Azure Free Account allow you to host production-based resources?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your company is planning to use Azure AD for the\nauthentication of the resources defined in Azure.\nDoes Azure AD have the capabilities to implement\nauthorization using Azure RBAC to secure resources?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does the Azure AD Premium P2 tier guarantee any Azure AD\nServices available with the availability higher than 99.99%?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company plans to upgrade its current Azure AD Free plan to the Azure AD Premium P1 plan.\nDoes Microsoft provide the same feature set for both plans?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to try out some services which Azure is offering in Public Preview.\nDo the services in Public Preview in Azure come with an SLA?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to try out some services which Azure is offering in preview.\nDoes Microsoft provide a separate portal to work with preview features?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your company needs to deploy and manage several\nAzure Web apps using the Azure App service resource.\nWhich of the following URL would you use to manage the Azure Web Apps?",
    "options": {
      "A": "https://portal.microsoft.com",
      "B": "https://portal.azure.com",
      "C": "https://portal.azurewebsites.net",
      "D": "https://portal.azurewebsites.com"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company needs to store 2 TB worth of data that is infrequently used.\nThe data needs to be accessed via Power BI.\nWhich of the following could be used as a cost-effective data layer for this requirement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure SQL databases",
      "B": "Azure PostgreSQL",
      "C": "Azure Cosmos DB",
      "D": "Azure Data Lake"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to ensure that their company's users are authenticated\nwhen they access resources defined in their Azure account.\nWhich of the following is the correct definition of authentication?",
    "options": {
      "A": "This specifies the type of service you can use in Azure.",
      "B": "This specifies the type of data you can use in Azure.",
      "C": "This is the act of providing legitimate credentials.",
      "D": "This specifies what you can do in Azure."
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to create several Virtual Machines in Azure.\nWhich of the following is the right category to which the Azure Virtual Machine belongs?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Infrastructure as a service (IaaS)",
      "B": "Platform as a service (PaaS)",
      "C": "Software as a service (SaaS)",
      "D": "Function as a service (FaaS)"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company needs to create around 50 customized Virtual Machines.\nOut of these, only 20 are Windows-based Virtual machines which are identical,\nand 30 are Ubuntu Machines, again of identical configuration.\nAll virtual machines will be used in a load-balanced configuration.\nWhich of the following would help reduce the administrative effort required to deploy the machines?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Load Balancer",
      "B": "Azure Web Apps",
      "C": "Azure Traffic Manager",
      "D": "Azure Scale sets"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to use Azure for the deployment of various solutions.\nThey want to ensure that whenever users authenticate to Azure, they have to use Multi-Factor Authentication.\nWhich of the following can help them achieve this?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Service Trust Portal",
      "B": "Azure Security Centre",
      "C": "Azure DDoS protection",
      "D": "Azure Privileged Identity Management"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to host 2 Virtual Machines in Azure.\nWould you still incur a cost on the storage?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true when it comes to SaaS?",
    "options": {
      "A": "You are responsible for scalability of the solution.",
      "B": "You are responsible for the maintenance of the underlying hardware",
      "C": "You are responsible for configuring the application settings.",
      "D": "You are responsible for the high availability of the solution."
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to set up an Enterprise Azure Subscription.\nDo they need to have a valid Microsoft Azure account on EA Portal\n(https://ea.azure.com/) for associating the Azure Subscription?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "An IT administrator for a company has been given a PowerShell script.\nThis PowerShell script will be used to create several Virtual Machines in Azure.\nYou have to provide a machine to the IT administrator for running the PowerShell script",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "An IT administrator for a company has been given a PowerShell script.\nThis PowerShell script will be used to create several Virtual Machines in Azure.\nYou have to provide a machine to the IT administrator for running the PowerShell script.\nYou decide to provide a LinuxOS-based machine (with Ubuntu) and use Azure Cloud Shell.\nWould this solution fit the requirement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "An IT administrator for a company has been given a PowerShell script.\nThis PowerShell script will be used to create several Virtual Machines in Azure.\nYou have to provide a machine to the IT administrator for running the PowerShell script.\nYou decide to provide an Azure CLI installed on a computer that has MacOS 10.13 and PowerShell 7.0.3 also installed.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "You decide to provide an Azure CLI installed on a computer that has MacOS 10.13 and PowerShell 7.0.3 also installed.\nAn Integration solution for the deployment of code.\nWhich of the following would be best suited for this requirement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Advisor",
      "B": "Azure Cognitive Services",
      "C": "Azure Application Insights",
      "D": "Azure DevOps"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to set up a solution in Azure.\nThe solution would have the following key requirement.\nA tool that provides guidance and recommendations to improve an Azure environment.\nWhich of the following would be best suited for this requirement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Advisor",
      "B": "Azure Cognitive Services",
      "C": "Azure Application Insights",
      "D": "Azure Devops"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to set up a solution in Azure.\nThe solution would have the following key requirement.\nA simplified tool to build intelligent Artificial Intelligence applications.\nWhich of the following would be best suited for this requirement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Advisor",
      "B": "Azure Cognitive Services",
      "C": "Azure Application Insights",
      "D": "Azure Devops"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to set up a solution in Azure.\nThe solution would have the following key requirement.\nA tool used to monitor Web applications hosted in production-based environments.\nWhich of the following would be best suited for this requirement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Advisor",
      "B": "Azure Cognitive Services",
      "C": "Azure Application Insights",
      "D": "Azure Devops"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company needs to implement a solution in Azure.\nBelow are the key requirements for this solution.\nNo need for schema or Index management.\nEnsure low latency access to data from around the world.\nWhich of the following data solution would you consider for this requirement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure SQL Database",
      "B": "Azure CosmosDB",
      "C": "Azure SQL Datawarehouse",
      "D": "SQL Server Stretch database"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to deploy Azure resources to a resource group.\nBut the resources would belong to different locations.\nCan you have resources that belong to the same resource group but be in multiple locations?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to deploy Azure resources to a resource group.\nThe company is planning to assign tags to the resource groups.\nWould the resources in the resource group also inherit the same tags?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is planning to deploy Azure resources to a resource group.\nThe company is planning to assign permissions to the resource groups.\nWould the resources in the resource group also inherit the same permissions?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No",
      "C": null,
      "D": null
    },
    "answer": "A"
  }
]
